https://www.retaininternational.com/privacy

We detected an old browser!This website doesn't support Internet Explorer 8 and older.Please upgrade your Internet Explorer to the latest version in order to enjoy this website.
Home
Introducing Retain 7.2
Features
Intuitive interface
Powerful tools
Tailored to you
Customers
Industries
r
NEW Retain Cloud. Next generation resource planning.
Retain Cloud
Contact Us
About Us
Careers
News
a
j
r
Privacy Policy
Retain International (“Retain”, “we”, “us”, “our”) is part of Capita Plc. This website www.retaininternational.com. (“website”) is owned and operated by Retain. Please read this Privacy Policy, together with our Terms of Use and Cookie Policy, with care before you use this website. If you do not wish to accept this Privacy Policy, please do not use the website. If you submit your personal information through this website, you are consenting to it being processed in the manner described within this Privacy Policy.
Retain realises the importance of providing you with a clear and honest explanation of what personal information we collect from you, how we use it, where we store it and for how long, whether or not we share your information with anyone else and what rights you have over your personal information. Personal information means information from which someone else would be able to identify you as an individual.
This Privacy Policy explains how we look after your personal information in more detail when you click on the relevant link below:
Who collects your personal information?
How do we collect your personal information?
What personal information do we collect about you?
How do we use your personal information?
What is the legal reason which allows us to use your personal information in a certain way?
Curriculum Vitae
Where do we store your personal information?
How long do we keep hold of your personal information?
Do we share or disclose your personal information?
Marketing
How can you access your personal information?
How can you ask for your personal information to be corrected or deleted?
Your rights over your personal information
Other websites
Cookies
Complaints procedure
This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies and organisations that we do not own, manage or control, or to people that we do not employ or manage.
We keep this Privacy Policy under regular review and so you should check these pages from time to time to keep you up to date with any changes. This Privacy Policy was last updated in November 2018.
Please contact us if you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, any personal information we hold about you or if you wish us to stop processing any personal information at:
info@retaininternational.com
Capita - Retain International, 65 Gresham St, London EC2V 7NQ, United Kingdom
Who collects your personal information?
Retain International (“Retain”) is part of Capita Plc. Retain collects the personal information from you and decides what to do with it. In compliance with Data Protection legislation, Retain is the Data Controller.
Our Registered Office address is: 65 Gresham St, London EC2V 7NQ, United Kingdonw (company number 01593831).
You can contact us at:
Capita - Retain International
65 Gresham St,LondonEC2V 7NQ
United Kingdom
Telephone number: +44 20 7538 4774
Email us at info@retaininternational.com
Our Data Protection Officer is Jenny Coombs who can be contacted at jenny.coombs@capita.co.uk
How do we collect your personal information?
Retain may collect your personal information when we meet you face to face, when you contact us either on the telephone or in writing, when you visit or use our website pages and when you use our services. We also collect information from you when you voluntarily complete customer feedback surveys.
We also automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the pages on our website you visited.
What personal information do we collect about you?
Retain may collect your name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, employer’s name, work postal address and work email address.
We also automatically receive and record your IP address, cookie information and information regarding which pages on our website you access and when.
If you send your Curriculum Vitae to us we may also collect other personal details including your date of birth and National Insurance number.
When we enter into a contract with you and need to process payment from you, we may also collect financial details including bank account details.
How do we use your personal information?
Retain takes your privacy seriously and we will only use your personal information in the following ways:
to deal with your enquiries and fulfil your requests for certain services and information
to send you communications which you have requested
to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts we enter into with you
to process payment from you
to request feedback from you on the services we provide
to notify you of changes to our services
to comply with the law
for marketing purposes
to consider your suitability for employment purposes
to monitor behaviour on our website (see our Cookie policy for more details)
Please be aware, if you choose to withhold your personal information when we require it, we may not be able to provide you with the services you have requested.
What is the legal reason which allows us to use your information in a certain way?
Legitimate purpose
We collect and use your personal information for the legitimate business purposes of communicating with you to deal with your enquiries, fulfilling your requests for services and information, sending you communications which you have requested, notifying you of changes to our services, processing payment from you where applicable and monitoring behaviour on our website to improve your browsing experience, help us to improve our website and make our marketing campaigns more relevant.
Contract
We may also need to use your personal information to perform our contract(s) with you so that we can carry out our obligations arising from any contract(s) we enter into with you or take initial steps at your request prior to entering into a contract(s).
Consent
We may also use your personal information where you give us your express consent.
Legal obligation
We will use your personal information where we have to comply with the law e.g. we have to provide information to HMRC or to fraud agencies etc.
You have a right to object to Retain processing your personal information and if you wish to object, please contact us at info@retaininternational.com
Curriculum Vitae
If you wish us to consider you for employment within Retain, we will need to use your personal information contained within any Curriculum Vitae you send to us to consider your suitability for and to discuss with you such employment.
Where do we store your personal information?
Here at Retain, we are committed to making sure that your personal information is kept secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure and to protect against loss we use up-to-date industry procedures to keep personally identifiable information as safe and secure as possible. We will use our best endeavours to protect your personal information but we cannot guarantee its security on transmission to the website. Any transmission is at your own risk.
We store your personal information on our servers in our data centres based in the UK. Personal information is also backed up in encrypted format and stored with Disaster Recovery Services Limited (DRS) based in the UK.
We may also store your personal information with Microsoft Office 365, a cloud service provider who will store the personal information within the European Economic Union.
We may also store your personal information with Microsoft Azure, a cloud service provider, who will store the personal information within the UK.
Our website is hosted in the UK with a G-Cloud 9 approved supplier at an ultra-secure data centre with Cyber essentials status and the following accreditations:
ISO 27018
ISO 27001:2013
ISO 14001:2015
How long do we keep hold of your personal information?
We will hold your personal information only for as long as is necessary to provide our services, although sometimes we are required by law to keep your personal information for longer to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements. We review our retention periods for personal information on a regular basis. Please contact us at info@retaininternational.com if you require any further information about our retention periods.
Do we share or disclose your personal information?
Retain will not sell or rent your personal information to anyone. All the personal information we hold about you will be processed by our staff in the United Kingdom. We will send personal information about you to other companies or people only when:
we have your consent to share the information
we need to share your information to provide the product(s) or service(s) you have requested
we need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of Retain to provide a product or service to you (unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personal information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us)
we respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process
we find that your actions on our web sites violate our Terms of Use, or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services.
Your personal data will not be transferred outside of the UK or the European Economic Area.
Marketing
We would like to use your personal information to send you marketing information about our products and services. This information will not be shared with third parties.
If you do consent to us sending you marketing information you still have the right to object to direct marketing at any time and you can withdraw your consent at any time. Once you withdraw your consent, we will not contact you further for marketing purposes but this will not affect any personal information that has already been processed up to that point.
You can change your marketing preferences or ask us to stop contacting you for marketing purposes at any time by contacting us at info@retaininternational.com or telephone on +44 20 7538 4774.
How can you access your personal information?
You have a right to access your personal information by making a Subject Access Request to Retain at any time you wish to see what personal information we hold about you and how we are using it so you can be satisfied it is being processed lawfully. You can ask for copies of this information and we will usually provide it free of charge and within one month of the date we receive your request (unless there are exceptional circumstances when we may then charge a reasonable fee to cover administrative charges or advise you that we require longer to deal with your request).
If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information you should send your Subject Access Request to info@retaininternational.com or write to us at Capita - Retain International, Barnard's Inn, 86 Fetter Lane, London, EC4A 1EN, United Kingdom.
Please ensure that you provide as much detail as possible about the personal information you wish to see and provide necessary proof of identification to enable us to deal with your request promptly.
How can you ask for your personal information to be corrected or deleted?
Retain want to make sure that your personal information is accurate. If you believe that the personal information we hold about you is inaccurate or incomplete, you have a right to ask us to correct it for you (right to rectification). Please contact us at info@retaininternational.com if you want to make such a request.
You also have a right to ask Retain to delete your personal information (right to erasure) and you should you contact us at info@retaininternational.com if you want to make such a request.
Your rights over your personal information
When you give your personal information to Retain, under Data Protection legislation you have the following rights in relation to your personal information - right to be informed, right of access, right to rectification, right to erasure, right to restrict processing, right to data portability, right to object and rights in relation to automated decision making and profiling. Some of these rights have already been referred to above in this Privacy Policy. For more information please visit: https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/individual-rights/
Please send any enquiries or requests in relation to these rights to info@retaininternational.com
Other websites
This website may contain links to and from other websites but please be aware that once you use any of these links to leave our website, those other websites have their own privacy policies and we do not have any control over those other websites. We cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting other websites so when you link to those other websites, you should read their own privacy policies.
Cookies
Our website uses Cookies. A Cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we put on your device when you visit our website and which collects information about how you browse our website. These Cookies allow us to recognise your device, help us to make your browsing experience better and improve our website.
Please see our Cookie Policy here.
Complaints procedure
We will advise you of the reason why we cannot comply with your request(s) if necessary.
If you wish to lodge a complaint on how we have handled your personal information or dealt with your request you can contact us at Capita - Retain International, 65 Gresham St, London EC2V 7NQ, United Kingdom, United Kingdom or telephone +44 20 7538 4774 or email us at info@retaininternational.com
We will endeavour to deal with your complaint at the earliest opportunity.
If you are not satisfied with our response or you believe we are not processing your personal information in accordance with current data protection legislation you can complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office at https://ico.org.uk/.
Benefits
Schedule in easy wallchart format
Talent management
Multi-platform
Better reporting and forecasting
More benefits
Security and access levels
Integration with ERP systems
Planning for:
Business type:
Select your Business Type
partnership (3 or more Partners)
partnership (2 or less Partners)
Privacy notice.
Increasing visibility, efficiency and operational capacity at Fera Science Limited (Fera) – a Retain International case study
© 2020 Retain International.
Company number: 01593831.
Thank You!
We'll be in touch shortly. In the meantime, feel free to connect with us on social media to stay updated on our latest releases.
a
j
r
